# **Adam Kogut**

Detail-oriented software engineer with 2+ years of experience in design, development, and testing of medical device software systems. Experienced in various platforms, languages, and development tools. Able to effectively self-manage in independent projects as well as collaborate in small teams in a remote setting.

### ajkogut@comcast.net

Adamkogut.com Noblesville, IN

#### **EXPERIENCE**

### **The RND Group,** Indianapolis, Indiana Software Engineer

JUNE 2020 - PRESENT

- Collaborated in small teams (up to 8) in a semi-agile environment to develop integrated software for medical devices
- Developed, tested, debugged, and documented 8 client applications with multiple projects going at a time
- Aided in critical decisions centering around asset hiring and development pathways for multiple client projects
- Developed frontend applications in React.js, Razor Pages, WinForms, and WPF to enhance the experience of clients and users
- Worked directly with clients to implement and guide the upgrade of critical systems to better match current UI/UX and performance patterns

## **The RND Group,** Indianapolis, Indiana Software Engineer Intern

MAY 2019 - SEPTEMBER 2019

- Updated the company's internal code review tool to learn .net and the rest of the technologies utilized by The RND Group
- Led a group of two fellow interns to create a tool to assist in the usage and administration of a project for a client
- Led the development of a client requested feature
- Used various industry technologies e.g. MVVM, Microsoft Prism, WPF, C#

# **Franciscan Alliance,** Indianapolis, Indiana Software Engineer Intern

MAY 2018 - AUGUST 2018

- Won the Bright Light award for my work at the company
- Updated front-end integration tests to the newest year
- Wrote front-end integration tests for the Epic Hyperspace system
- Helped upgrade the team's notes from word to Microsoft OneNote
- Led the team's upgrade to a version control service (GitHub)

#### **Skills**

- Relational databases
- Unit and integration testing
- Development on Linux and Windows OSes
- Application debugging
- C#
- React.js
- JavaScript
- TypeScript
- Git
- WPF
- WinForms

#### **EDUCATION**

Purdue University, West Lafayette, Indiana BS in Computer Science

AUGUST 2016 -MAY 2020